Guide to the Jerry Retzloff Collection
The Wittliff Collections
Jerry Retzloff Collection
1973-2012
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Retzloff, Gerald "Jerry"
SWWC.113
28 Linear Feet
20 boxes (plus 1 oversized folder)
The Jerry Retzloff Collection spans 1973-2012 and documents Texas music, Lone Star Beer, and Willie Nelson. The collection is arranged in nine series: Personal Papers, Lone Star Beer, Photographs, Willie Nelson, Memorabilia, Oversized Materials, Newspapers and Magazines, Clothing, and Posters.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Jerry Retzloff, 2014
Biographical / Historical
Jerry Retzloff was born in San Antonio, Texas, on January 4, 1940 to Walter (Red) and Celia Retzloff. He was raised on the Southeast side of town, proudly attending Central Catholic High School. Upon graduation, Jerry decided to join the U.S. Coast Guard and was stationed in San Francisco, California. He enjoyed the USCG and often spoke pridefully of being the only coasty to have never gotten seasick on his ship despite numerous significant storms on his watch. During one storm, he wagered everyone their once-a-week ration of steak that he would not get seasick – he won the bet and ate steaks daily for over a month.
Upon returning from the USCG, he came back to San Antonio and joined Lone Star Brewery in 1963. He loved his job at Lone Star Beer, working on the dock, the accounting office, and ultimately ending up in marketing and special promotions. While at Lone Star in his early years, he also earned his bachelor's degree in marketing from St. Mary's University. In the mid 1970s, he became the district manager for Lone Star in Austin, Texas. He worked passionately to grow the brand through the burgeoning Austin music scene. Jerry identified with the younger crowd and made connections quickly - enjoying music, meeting people, building relationships and promoting the "National Beer of Texas". He developed many bonds with musicians from the area including Kinky Friedman, Red Stegall, Charlie Daniels, and, among others, his lifelong friend, Willie Nelson.
Jerry originated the concept of calling beer bottles "long necks" and promoted the idea of "Long Live Long Necks". He was especially proud to have been featured in an article for Texas Monthly (2014) entitled "Bottle Rocket" - an amazing article on how Jerry built the Lone Star brand through music, unique promotions and his travels from Austin to Nashville to Hollywood. To cap his legendary career in the beer/music business, a phenomenal exhibit was created in his honor at Texas State University's Wittliff Collections.
After retiring with 34 years at Lone Star Beer, Jerry pursued his hobby of fishing and telling stories on frequent trips to the Rockport area. He also served in the hospital ministry at the downtown Baptist Hospital for 26 years. Having built a vast network of friends over the years, he genuinely enjoyed people, had a servant's heart, was kind to all and never encountered a stranger. His trademark phrase of "Not to Worry" stuck with him until the end. He passed away March 10, 2020.
[From obituary, March 2020]
Scope and Contents
The Jerry Retzloff Collection spans 1973-2012 and documents Texas music, Lone Star Beer, and Willie Nelson. The collection is arranged in nine series: Personal Papers, Lone Star Beer, Photographs, Willie Nelson, Memorabilia, Oversized Materials, Newspapers and Magazines, Clothing, and Posters.
Index Terms
Subjects
Collectors and collecting; Country music; Beer; Advertising
Subjects (Persons)
Nelson, Willie, 1933-
Subjects (Corporations)
Lone Star Brewing Company
- Personal Papers, undated
  Series Description
  Personal Papers include resumes, letters, notes, and ephemera.
  - Resume, address lists, artist contacts, business cards (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letters, greeting cards (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notes (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Printed items, souvenirs (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Lone Star Beer, 1973-2007
  Series Desciption
  Lone Star Beer records document the history of the San Antonio brewery through printed material, memos, photographs, publications, and advertisements – many of which feature Texas musicians.
  - History of Lone Star Beer (29 pages) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barry Sullivan - resume, packet from Eddie Wilson (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memos and correspondence, 1974-1989, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photographs [chili cook-off, vans, corporate groups] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Publications and printed material, 1973-1990
    - The Bruit Magazine, Spring 1973, Winter 1976, November 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - On Tap, [Features Six Pak, vol. 1 album cover with inside article, "Lone Star Sippin and Skinny Dippin" (2 copies), December 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Lone Star Brewery housing brochure (2 copies) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Footnotes of the Buckhorn: A Lone Star State Landmark, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Invitation to the Second General Convention of Funseekers, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Postcard for the Buckhorn Bar (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "A Little Bit of Texas" card with artwork by Sam Yeates (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Beer labels [various Lone Star labels, as well as Colt 45, Schmidt's, Mickey's, and Mexicali] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Print Advertisements, 1977-1988
    Related Materials
    Oversize print advertisements are in box 9
    - Texas Girl magazine featuring Willie Nelson on cover; ad on back. Artwork by Sam Yeates, December 1979 (Box 1, Item 11)
    - Movement magazine; ad on back, Artwork by Sam Yeates, May 1978 (Box 1, Item 11)
    - Table tents (2 copies), 1988 (Box 1, Item 11)
    - Austin Sun back cover ads (clipped): Commander Cody, Willie Nelson, and "You're never alone with Lone Star" (Box 1, Item 11)
    - "Deep in the Heritage…A Texas Tradition" (clipped). Artwork by Sam Yeates, 1977 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - Radio Advertisement: 10 CD copies of cassette tapes that include Lone Star commercials "Long Live Long Necks" lyrics. Glenn Advertising, April 17, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publicity packet for the "Lone Star Country Music Special" featuring Willie Nelson, Sammi Smith, Rusty Wier, B.W. Stevenson, Asleep at the Wheel, Steve Fromholz, Willis Alan Ramsey, and Jimmy Buffett, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Advertising Photographs
    Oversized advertising photographs are in box 9
    - Models (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Janet Quist (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Print articles about Lone Star and brewing (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Oversize articles and newspapers are in box 5
  - Terrence York packet regarding Silver Eagles Taking Flight [letter, photocopy of publication, 4 photographs] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Country Music Association – Organization member certificate, programs, October 13, 1975 and October 11, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Contents
    The 1976 program has many signatures including Charley Pride, Bobbie Nelson, Jody Payne, Roy Clark, Freddy Fender, and Waylon Jennings.
- Photographs, 1976-1986, undated
  Photographs are arranged by subject, featuring Retzloff with various performers, Willie Nelson, and other musicians performing and off-stage. Oversized photographs are in boxes 9 and 12.
  - Jerry Retzloff
    - Photographs of Jerry Retzloff (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Jerry Retzloff with performers/artists
      - Backstage at the CMA awards with Ray Charles, B.J. Thomas, Kris Kristofferson, George Strait, and Charley Pride, 1986 (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Barbi Benton, model [negative, slide, 3 x 5 photograph, 8 x 10 photograph] (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Charlie Daniels (Box 2, Item 4)
      - James Garner, actor (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Loretta Lynn (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Louise Mandrell (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Janet Quist [Lone Star model] (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Susan Saint James, actress (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Cat Sundeen, radio personality (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Conway Twitty (Box 2, Item 4)
      - Stevie Ray Vaughan (Box 2, Item 4)
    - Jerry Retzloff with other individuals
      - Funseekers Mike Bixby, unidentified, and Retzloff, Canyon Lake, Texas (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Lone Star special events personnel, 1980 (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Ralph York, recording engineer for Red Headed Stranger, 1981 (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Roger Collins, partner in One Nite Bar & Dive, Austin (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Tip of Texas trail ride [Special Events Department], 1978 (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Stan Retzloff, Texas Independence Day party, La Vallita, San Antonio, 1986 (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Tip of Texas trail ride, TU Presentation, unidentified, 1980s (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Larry Trader, Pedernales Country Club/Golf Club manager (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Funseeker Dee ____ (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Pappy Yoakum, owner of truck fleet, Florida. Nashville at the CMA awards, 1976 (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Russ Clanton, Lone Star distributer, Conroe Texas (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Dave Davis, Austin (Box 2, Item 5)
      - Gair Allee, Lone Star sales at armadillo race (Box 2, Item 5)
    - Retzloff with various groups (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "In Luck [Texas] with Casey and the Boys" (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Darrell Royal Gold Tournament [snapshots of attendees, crowd, and performers - Special Events Department] (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Willie Nelson
    - Photographs of Willie Nelson [Includes candid snapshots, picture of Nelson with Lone Star beer and talking to reporter, Nelson in studio after listening to Red Headed Stranger recording, promotional portrait from RCA] (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Willie Nelson with Retzloff [candid snapshots including series of 3 photos where Willie asks if he wants to "burn one."] (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Willie Nelson with Darrell Royal, Leon Russell, and unidentified individuals (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Nelson performing at Lone Star sales meetings [2 different years] (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Nelson performing [includes photo of Nelson at CMAs taken by Retzloff] (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Performers - Identified
    - Jimmy Buffett [CBS publicity packet including 4 photographs] (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Charlie Daniels Band (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Cheap Trick (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Kinky Friedman (Box 2, Item 15)
    - New England (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Jody Payne (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Leon Russell (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Sammi Smith (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Rusty Wier (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Steve Wilson [Terror and the Cat] (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Neil Young (Box 2, Item 15)
  - Performers - Publicity Photos
    - Asleep at the Wheel (2) (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Baillie and the Boys [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Clarence Gatemouth Brown [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Freddy Fender [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Foster and Lloyd [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Steven Fromholz with Susan Saint James [Good Buddies still] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - James Garner [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Alan Jackson [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Wynona and Naomi Judd [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Last Chance Band [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Louise Mandrell [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Johnny Paycheck [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Billy Walker [signed] (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Jerry Jeff Walker (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Unidentified band (Box 3, Item 1)
  - Performers – Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photos of others (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
- Willie Nelson
  Willie Nelson includes souvenirs, programs, and published books, documenting his music career, association with Lone Star Beer, and friendship with Jerry Retzloff.
  - Souvenirs, 1978, undated
    - Caesar's Palace program featuring Willie Nelson & Family (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Caesar's Palace reserved seating sign for Willie Nelson (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Golden Nugget table tent featuring Willie Nelson in the Gold Strike Lounge (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Ramada Airport hotel, Corpus envelope. Room 270, "Wild, Bill" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Flattened Supertape recording box "Willie Nelson Corpus Christie Tex Live, 1-4-78" Signed for Retzloff's birthday, January 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Neil Hickey business card w/ notes re: TV Guide photo of Nelson (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Willie Nelson & Family notepad (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Golf score card (blank) from Pedernales Country Club (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Notecard (blank) featuring "Willie Blue Skies" painting by Steve Brooks (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1974-1975, 1986, undated
    - Bralley Ranch First Annual Fourth of July Picnic [front and back cover only; Lone Star Beer ad on back cover] (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Willie Nelson's Second Annual Fourth of July Picnic, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Willie Nelson's Third Annual Fourth of July Picnic (7 copies) [Inside back cover has mail in form for Lone Star schooner poster by Jim Franklin], 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Wrangler presents Willie Nelson and Family, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Willie Nelson Official Discography (3 copies), 1982, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Press Packets: CBS Records (2 copies; one in envelope); Columbia Records (in envelope) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Published Books, 1976, 1980
    - The Best of Willie Nelson, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Willie Nelson Songbook, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Willie Nelson Family Album, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Memorabilia
  Memorabilia includes a wide array of music ephemera including ticket stubs, backstage passes, badves, bumper stickers, pins and buttons, belt buckles, matchbooks, guitar picks, audio cassettes, and more.
  - Travel luggage tags: Puerta Vallarta, Mexico; Las Vegas, Nashville, New Orleans (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Clubs, Businesses
    - Duke's menu (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Inner Sanctum Records business card for James Cooper (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Plaza Hotel: restaurant and room service menus (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - St. James Club advertisement (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Sunset Marquis postcard (blank) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Texas Hatters catalog (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Union Plaza hotel folded letter (blank) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - White House office of the Vice President letterhead (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ticket stubs, 1974-2009
    - Waylon Jennings, Billy Joe Shaver & Ray Wylie Hubbard. Lone Star Jamboree, Dallas, Texas, June 1, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Charlie Daniels Band. Volunteer Jam, Middle Tennessee State University Murphy Center, Murfreesboro, Tennessee, September 12, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - ZZ Top. Fandango, Memorial Auditorium, Dallas, [ticket taped to invitation at post concert party at the Electric Ballroom], November 29, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Willie & Waylon Live at the Summit, December 31, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Charley Pride. Municipal Auditorium, Austin, January 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Waylon Jennings, Amazing Rhythm Aces. Gregory Gym, Austin, April 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Willie Nelson. Benefit for a Friend. Gilley's, Pasadena, Texas, April 8, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Willie Nelson's Picnic. Day 3. Cotton Bowl, Dallas, Texas, July 3, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Electric Horseman, Caesar's Palace [Invitation], December 22, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - ZZ Top. Expect No Quarter. Convention Center Arena, San Antonio, January 4, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - United States Capitol, Washington D.C. (2 tickets), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - National Air and Space Museum (3 tickets), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Vice President's Gallery [Walter Mondale], 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - ZZ Top. Expect No Quarter, December 29, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Willie Nelson. Reunion Arena, Dallas, Texas, December 30, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Houston Livestock Show and Rodeo, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Neil Young. Convention Center Arena, San Antonio, July 18, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Texas Renaissance Festival. The King's Gourmet Feast, October 1, 1983 and October 6, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - One Knite Reunion. Benefit for Musicares. Stubbs Waller Creek, Austin (2 tickets), May 23, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Charlie Daniels Band. Longneck Legends with Kevin Fowler. Concrete Street Amphitheater [3 tickets plus envelope], June 12, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Columbia / Epic / Monument Records: The Nashville Family of Music. Dinner show, October 18, [no year], Municipal Auditorium (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Terlingua International Chili Cookoff. [3 judges certificates], November 3, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Backstage passes, badges, 1980-2009, undated
    - CMA Awards Show [Willie Nelson's guest], 1983 and 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Charlie Daniels Band, January 12, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Charlie Daniels Band, January 8 [no year] (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Charlie Daniels Band [6 badges], 2007-2013 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Indie Bash and Brew at the Brewery, October 24, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Willie Nelson and Family [First picnic? Name badge with photo] (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Willie Nelson and Family, Palladium, Dallas, February 26, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - [Willie Nelson, Del Rio] VIP Parking, October 21, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Willie Nelson, San Antonio, December 3, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Willie Nelson Backstage Pass (metal), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - One Knite Reunion (2 VIP passes), May 23, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Merriweather Post Pavilion, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hank Wilks (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Wrist band (green, orange, white) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Artist badge (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sew and iron on badges, 1978-1982, undated
    - Lone Star: 2 small badges; 1 large; 1 "Lone Star 150 Private Stock" (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - American Flag (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Texas Flag (2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Caesar (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Charlie Daniels Band Volunteers [large] (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Waylon (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Welcome to Backstage Texas [artwork by Jim Franklin] (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Viva Terlingua (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Texas Hatters "We Top the Best" [large] (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Texas Opry House [iron on] (3) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Tarpon Rodeo, South Padre Island (2), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - South Padre Island Billfish Association, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Port Mansfield Fishing Tournament (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Port Aransas Deep Sea Round up, 1978 and 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Premium Quality Certified (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Travis County Constable (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bumper stickers
    - Lone Star Beer (19) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Willie Nelson (11) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Winters Brothers Band (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - David Allen Coe (3) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Charlie Daniels Band (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "I Shot JR" [Dallas television show] (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Alliance Wagon Yard, Austin (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "I Love Jill" (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "Live Music is Better" (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "Official Car: U.S. Secret Service" (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - KOKE FM (3) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Pins and buttons, 1980-2006
    - Lone Star Beer [bottle] (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Texas Sesquicentennial [Texas flag] (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Lone Star Light [State of Texas] (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Southern Trailriders [Horseshoe] (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - State of Texas with confederate stripes (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Lone Star [Armadillo in State of Texas] 2 copies (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Armadillo pin [Gift of Bob Dylan] (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Go Western Gala [State of Texas], 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Fiesta San Antonio, April 14-25, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Willie Nelson lettering (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Merle Haggard (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Smiley Face (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lone Star [Armadillo] (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The San Antonio [Rose] [State of Texas] (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Texas Hatters (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Carter/Mondale/Willie Nelson [green circle], October 12, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lone Star [red, plastic] (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lone Star [Armadillo holding bottle] (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lone Star Beer [blue oval] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Willie and Family: Me and Paul Productions [State of Texas] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lone Star, Texas Aggies [bottle] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lone Star [boot] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Republic of Texas Chilymiad [white State of Texas] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lone Star Beer [Bottle cap] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lone Star Light Beer [blue with white lettering] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - K-BUC AM 1310/FM 107.5 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Tennis shoe with wings (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Armadillo (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lone Star [bottle] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lone Star Light [blue, plastic] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Neil Young Solo Tour (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Canadian Flag (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - World Class Hobie Association [Lone Star sponsored Hobie Cat] (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Alabama / RCA (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Rolling Thunder Revue [4 buttons: yellow, red, green, orange] (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Stevie Ray Vaughan, World Premiere Album Riverboat Cruise, April 17, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 344 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Willie Nelson [photo] (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lone Star: The National Beer of Texas (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Yo Santa. Jingle This (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lone Star 150: Private Stock Beer (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Viva Terlingua! Behind the store in '84 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Lone Star Beer. Let's Rodeo (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Kinky [Friedman] for Governor, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - One More in '74 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Willie Nelson Live, Caesar's Palace (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Willie Nelson "The King of Luck" (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Firefall (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Charlie Daniels Band. Saddle Tramp (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Peter Frampton "I'm In You" (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Not to Worry [Yellow circle] (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Out to Lunch (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Charlie Daniels Band. On Stage (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Not to Worry [white circle] (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Jerry Retzloff nametag for Houston Pod Casi Hot Stuff (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Jerry Retzloff sponsor nametag for the Darrell [Royal] & Willie [Nelson] Invitational (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Jerry Retzloff paperweight business card (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - San Antonio Livestock Show and Rodeo, calf scramble, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - San Antonio Conservation Society (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Houston Livestock Show and Rodeo. Trail Ride Committee (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Whiskey Flats Honorary Sheriff, Kernville, CA (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Houston Livestock Show and Rodeo "Committeeman" nametags, (8 nametags), 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
  - Lone Star beer cuff links [?], Gerald Ford tie clip (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Official Lone Star Drinking Glove (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Belt buckles, 1975, 1986, undated
    - Willie Nelson [tennis shoes] (Box 6)
    - Texas Hatters (Box 6)
    - Grand Ole Opry. 50 Years (Box 6)
    - Texas Sesquicentennial, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Lone Star Beer. Kinky Friedman "Texas Jew Boy" acrylic with scorpions (Box 6)
    - Lone Star Beer [shield] (Box 6)
    - Pull Tab buckle (Box 6)
    - Hoyt Axton (Box 6)
    - Rolling Thunder Revue (Box 6)
    - Unidentified, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Luckenbach Post Office (Box 6)
    - KEXL 104 ½ Stereo (Box 7)
    - Kessler American Whiskey (Box 7)
    - Maxell cassette tape (Box 7)
    - ZZ Top "That little band of Texas" (Box 7)
    - ZZ Top "Tejas" (Box 7)
    - Armadillo Van Clan (Box 7)
    - Drilling Tools, Inc. (Box 7)
    - Pearl inlay (Box 7)
    - Plain buckle (Box 7)
    - Darrell & Willie Invitational [luggage tag] (Box 7)
    - Horseman Officer. Houston Rodeo [badge] (Box 7)
  - Matchbooks and rolling paper
    - Hotel Riviera, Las Vegas, NV (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sportsman's Lodge, Studio City, CA (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Zig-Zag rolling paper (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Four Queens Hotel & Casino, Las Vegas, NV (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Oat Willie's, Austin (Box 8, Folder 1)